Guide to GMU Public Relations Press Releases
Copyright George Mason University Libraries
- GMU Public Relations- Press Releases
  - NPR'S ALAN CHEESE JOIN WRITING FACULTY AT GMU TURNER / ZIEMBA P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - FENWICK LIBRARY RECEIVES COMMUNITY CONTRIBUTIONS P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - SECOND NUCLEAR WAR EDUCATION CONFERENCE SCHEDULED AT GMU TURNER / ZIEMBA P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - INTERNATIONAL STUDENT PROGRAM SELECTS GMU SENIOR ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - PARK MANAGEMENT TRAINING PROGRAM AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - ARTS SUPPORTS HONORED AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - FABRIC AND THREAD EXHIBIT AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS SEPT. 15TH AT GMU ACKERMAN M.A. (Box Box 32)
  - VICE PRESEDENT FOR DEVELOPMENT APPOINTED AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - WATERCOLOR EXHIBIT AT GMU METRO GALLERY ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - POWER OUT FOR REPAIRS ACKERMAN FL. (Box Box 32)
  - GMU BUSINESS INCUBATOR WELCOMES FIRST PARTICIPANT ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 32)
  - CHEUSE READS ON CAMPUS ACKERMAN C.I. (Box Box 33)
  - COUNSELING AND TESTING AVAILABLE AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - BLACK LEADERSHIP CONFERENCE AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - BOOK ALERTS VIRGINIANS TO PUBLIC POLICY ISSUES OF 1990s TOWNSEND P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU OFFERS COURSE IN PSYCHIATRIC NURSING ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU HOLDS REVIEW COURSE FOR STATE NURSING BOARDS ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - PRIZE WINNING SHORT STORY AUTHOR / NOVELIST GIVES READING AT GMU TURNER / ZIEMBA. (Box Box 33)
  - LECTURE ON CONFLICT RESOLUTION INAUGURATES NEW CHAIR AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - WRITERS AT GEORGE MASON PROGRAM CONTINUES W/THREE WRITERS IN NOV. TURNER / ZIEMBA P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - PAINTINGS FROM THE PHILLIPS COLLECTION ON DISPLAY AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - MIDDLE EAST EXPERTS DISCUSS PERSIAN GULF WAR ACKERMAN C.I. (Box Box 33)
  - KGB DEFECTOR SPEAKS AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - VIRGINIA'S NOBEL LAUREATE REFUSES FLORIDA STATE OFFER ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GOVERNING BOARD MEETS AT GMU ACKERMAN M.A. (Box Box 33)
  - CENTENNIAL DEVELOPMENT CORP. DONATES FIRST OF $ 25,000 TO GMU'S SCHOOL OF BUSINESS ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - THREE NEW COMMONWEALTH PROFESSORS APPOINTED AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU A BEST BUY ACCORDING TO U.S. NEWS AND WORLD REPORT ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU'S COLLEGE OF EDUCATION AWARDED NATIONAL ACCREDITATION THROUGH 1992 ACKERMAN. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU LAW AND ECONOMICS CENTER RECEIVES GENERAL ELECTRIC GRANT ACKERMAN. (Box Box 33)
  - ABBY HOFFMAN TO SPEAK AT GMU ACKERMAN C.I. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU STUDENT ON NATIONAL FRATERNITY COUNCIL ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - SOME DISCOUNTED PERSONAL PHONES DISCONNECTED ACKERMAN FLASH. (Box Box 33)
  - SHARE YOUR HOLIDAY CELEBRATION WITH A GMU FOREIGN - STUDENT ACKERMAN P.S.A. C.I. (Box Box 33)
  - PULITZER PRIZE WINNING POET ESTABLISHES LITERARY PRIZE AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - NEW UNDERGRADUATE SYSTEMS ENGINEERING DEGREE AT GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU LAW DEAN RECEIVES HONORARY DEGREE ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - ARMS CONTROL AND THE US ACKERMAN M.A. (Box Box 33)
  - CHRISTMAS - NEW YEAR HOLIDAY CLOSING ACKERMAN FLASH. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU'S PAUL D' ANDREA WINS AWARD FROM THE FOUNDATION OF THE DRAMATISTS GUILD ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - NEW VIRGINIA - WIDE SCHOLARSHIP PROGRAM OFFERED BY GMU ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - NEW OFFERINGS AT GMU ADDRESS SHORTAGE OF NURSES ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - DOCTORAL PROGRAM IN CLINICAL PSYCHOLOGY RECEIVES ACCREDITATION TURNER / ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU ART STUDENTS CREATE MURAL FOR SHELTER ACKERMAN M.A. P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU EXTENDS PROGRAMS STATEWIDE GILLEY / ACKERMAN P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - ENGLISH LANGUAGE INSTITUTE HELPS STUDENTS, EMPLOYEES ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU GIVEN JOINT CUSTODY OF BREEN THEATER COLLECTION ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU CENTER TO TEACH EDUCATORS SUBSTANCE ABUSE PREVENTION METHODS ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU HOSTS ALUMNI ART EXHIBIT ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - HEMLOCK OVERLOOK: A SUCCESS STORY ROEBUCK P.R. (Box Box 33)
  - GMU HOLDS FINANCIAL AID WORKSHOP ACKERMAN P.S.A, C.I. (Box Box 33)
  - AUTHOR DONALD WOODS TO LECTURE AT GMU ON APARTHEID P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - NURSING UPDATE COURSES AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL OPENS NEW OFFICE OF DEVELOPMENT P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - PERFORMING ARTS DEPARTMENT MOVES F.L. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU AND FAIRFAX CO. SCHOOLS BEGIN NEW EARLY IDENTIFICATION PROGRAM P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU SCHOOL OF NURSING HOLDS OPEN HOUSE P.S.A (Box Box 34)
  - GMU STUDENTS JOIN PRESTIGIOUS WHO'S WHO HONOR ROLL P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU SUSPENDS CLASSES TO OBSERVE MARTIN LUTHER KING JR'S BIRTHDAY P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - COMMITTEE FORMED TO ADVISE ON FUTURE PLANS FOR GEORGE MASON METRO CAMPUS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - DULLES REGION TRANSPORTATION FORUM TO BE HELD AT GMU M.A. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS JAN. 19TH M.A. (Box Box 34)
  - FIRE ALARM TESTS F.L. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU DISTINGUISHED VISITING WRITER AWARDED 1987 EDITOR'S BOOK AWARD P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU DIRECTOR OF ENGLISH LANGUAGE INSTITUTE RECEIVED FULBRIGHT GRANT P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - WADE GILLEY NAMED PROVOST AT GEORGE MASON P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - TEACHING CONTRIBUTIONS OF RELIGIOUS GROUPS IN PUBLIC SCHOOLS TOPIC AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU CELEBRATES BLACK HISTORY MONTH P.R. / C.I. / P.S.A. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU HOSTS SWEETHEART WHEELCHAIR BASKETBALL TOURNAMENT P.R. /C.I. / P.S.A. (Box Box 34)
  - WARD EXHIBITS SCULPTURE AT MARIE MARTIN GALLERY P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU RECEIVES WINKLER SCHOLARSHIP P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU STUDENTS FUND RAISE FOR MENTALLY HANDICAPPED C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - AREA ARTISTS EXHIBIT WATERCOLORS AT GMU'S GALLERY C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU METRO CAMPUS HOSTS HIGH - TECH JOB FAIR C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - MASH ACCEPTS PRESIDENCY OF WAYNE STATE COLLEGE P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU RECEIVES DONATION FOR ECONOMIC RESEARCH FROM MARTIN - MARIETTA DATA SYSTEMS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - THE BLACK EXPERIENCE IN VIRGINIA HIGHLIGHTED EXHIBIT P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - RESEARCH JOURNAL "WOMEN AND LANGUAGE" RELOCATES TO GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - NEW OPPORTUNITIES FOR CONTRACTING IN THE SPACE - DEFENSE MARKET P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - "AIDS IN THE WORKPLACE CONFERENCE AT GMU" P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - OFFICE OF MANAGEMENT AND BUDGET DIRECTOR TO SPEAK AT GMU ALUMNI P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - JULI ROEBUCK NAMED ASSOCIATE DIRECTOR OF MEDIA RELATIONS AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU SPONSORS "CAREERS UNLIMITED 88" P.S.A. / P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - LECTURE SERIES FOCUSES ON THE CONSTITUTION C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - RIORDAN NAMED DEAN OF ADMISSIONS AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - "INDEPENDENT VISIONS: 10 ARTISTS AT GMU" P/R. (Box Box 34)
  - FORMER C AND P EXECUTIVE JOINS GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - MASON BASKETBALL MAKES TOURNAMENT FINALS F.L. (Box Box 34)
  - 1987 ALTERNATIVE NOBEL PEACE RECIPIENT HIGH LIGHTS GEORGE MASON'S INTERNATIONAL WEEK P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS AT METRO CAMPUS M.A. (Box Box 34)
  - NORTHERN VIRGINIA WRITING PROJECT OFFERS STUDENT SUMMER INSTITUTE AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - PROFESSIONAL ARTISTS EXHIBIT AT METRO CAMPUS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - COLLEGE FAIR FOR SENIOR HIGH SCHOOL STUDENTS HELD AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - RESEARCH SHOWS RADON LEVELS HIGH IN MANY AREA HOMES P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - EMINENT RUSSIAN AUTHOR ACCEPTS ROBINSON PROFESSORSHIP AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - DEADLINE FOR FY 87-88 PURCHASES FL. (Box Box 34)
  - CONTINUING EDUCATION COURSES FOR NURSES OFFERED BY GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - JURIED STUDENT EXHIBITION AT GMU C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU OFFERS TWO WORKSHOPS IN COPING SKILLS C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - ADD SOME CLASS TO YOUR SUMMER AT GMU P.R. /C.I. /P.S.A. (Box Box 34)
  - LECTURES SERIES ON NEW FRONTIERS IN COMP. TECH. TO BE PRESENTED AT GMU P.R. / P.S.A. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU WINS NATIONAL INVITATIONAL MOOT COURT TOURNAMENT P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU RECEIVES $50,000 FROM PHILLIP L. GRAHAM FUND P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - EDIBLE ART COMPETITION AND EXHIBIT AT GMU C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU'S PI KAPPA PHI FRATERNITY HAS FUNDRAISER FOR HANDICAPPED P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU OFFERS COUNSELING CONFERENCE C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - GEORGE MASON NAMES SCIENCE BUILDING DAVID J. KING HALL P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU TO HOST NATIONAL HISTORY DAY COMPETITION P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU ALUMNI ASSOCIATION HOLDS REUNION P.R. / P.S.A. (Box Box 34)
  - AUTHORS GIVEN READINGS AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - MARY ROBERTS RINEHART FUND SELECTS 1988 NATIONAL LITERARY COMPETITION WINNERS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - INTERNATIONAL EXPERTS GIVE CLASSICS LECTURE AT GMU C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU TO OFFER SYMPOSIUM ON TEACHING THE VIETNAM WAR P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - FUNDS RAISED FOR GMU'S CONFLICT RESOLUTION CENTER P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU OFFERS COMPUTER SEMINAR FOR TEACHERS C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU OFFERS HEALTH FAIR 1988 P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - LEWIS APPOINTED NEW DEAN OF COLLEGE OF ARTS AND SCIENCES AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - MEDICAL - SURGICAL NURSING REFRESHER COURSE OFFERED BY GMU C.I. (Box Box 34)
  - GEORGE MASON SCHOLAR RECIPIENT P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU TO GRADUATE LARGEST CLASS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU OFFERS DOCTORAL IN CONFLICT RESOLUTION P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - COMMUNITY COLLEGE PRESIDENT JOINS GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - COOPERATIVE EDUCATION WEEK TO BE OBSERVED BY STATE, GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS M.A. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU RECOGNIZES DONORS TO FAIRFAX COUNTY CHAIR OF LOCAL GOVERNMENT M.A. (Box Box 34)
  - WILLIAM HAZEL DONATES $ 1 MILLION TO GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU RAISES COSTS 6.3 PERCENT P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU FORENSICS TEAM PLACES IN NATION'S TOP 10. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU LAW SCHOOL GRADUATION SCHEDULED FOR MAY 28 P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - BURKE WOMEN NAMED GMU SECRETARY OF THE YEAR P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU CO - SPONSORS WELLNESS WALK FOR SENIOR CITIZENS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - NEW BASKETBALL COACH NAMED FL. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS M.A. (Box Box 34)
  - STUDENTS "EXCEL" GMU SUMMER PROGRAM P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - PRESIDENTIAL SCHOLARSHIPS OFFERED TO EIGHT OUTSTANDING STUDENTS AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GRADUATION FEATURE STORIES P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - LEARNING AS A LIFELONG PROCESS FOCUS OF CONFERENCE AT GMU P.R. / P.S.A. (Box Box 34)
  - NON - AVAILABILITY OF HOT MATTER FL. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU PROFESSOR FROM HERNDON WINS FELLOWSHIP P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - RARE MAPS EXHIBITION OPENS AT GMU LIBRARY GALLERY P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - RALLY TO WELCOME "RUN TO DAYLIGHT WINNER" DOUG WALKER TO NO. VA. P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU ESTABLISHES CENTER FOR ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - ACCESS TO CAMPUS PARKING DURING FAIRFAX COUNTY FAIR FL. (Box Box 34)
  - STUDENT REPRESENTATIVE APPOINTED TO GMU BOARD OF VISITORS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - BETHESDA WOMEN RECEIVES SCHOLARSHIP IN GMU GERONTOLOGY PROGRAM P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - NURSING CERTIFICATION REVIEW COURSE OFFERED BY GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - SUMMER COURSES FOR LEARNING DISABLED CHILDREN AND ADULTS OFFERED BY GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU HOLDS TWO WEEK COURSE ON TEACHING ABOUT RELIGION IN PUBLIC SCHOOLS P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU NAMES GEORGE WASHINGTON ARTS AND SCIENCES DEAN AS NEW PROVOST P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU HOSTS GOVERNOR'S ASIAN STUDIES ACADEMY P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - NEW EXHIBIT AT GMU'S METRO CAMPUS OPENS JULY 1ST P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - COMMUNITY COLLEGE EDUCATION PROGRAM DIRECTOR APPOINTED AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - VIRGINIA WESTERN COMMUNITY COLLEGE PRESEDENT SERVES AS EXECUTIVE INTERN AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 34)
  - GMU CONFERENCE EXAMINES MAN'S BASIC NEEDS IN EFFORT TO DEVELOP CONFLICT RESOLUTION FRAMEWORK P.R (Box Box 35)
  - 200 COMPETITORS EXPECTED AT GMU SUMMER OPEN CHESS TOURNAMENT JULY 23- 24 P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - METRO GALLERY HOSTS EXHIBIT OF VIRGINIA ARTIST BILL MATRZ P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - PRESS CONFERENCE (GMU AND SHENANDOAH) FL/P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - FIRE ALARMS TO BE TESTED P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - FACULTY MEMBER AWARDED FULBRIGHT GRANT IN KOREA P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - VIRGINIA INITIATIVE MEETING M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - VIOLIN AND PIANO RECITAL C.I. (Box Box 35)
  - ENGLISH LANGUAGE INSTITUTE IMPROVES SKILLS OF FOREIGN BORN EMPLOYEES P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - INTERNATIONALLY - KNOWN ANTHROPOLOGIST NAMED ROBINSON PROFESSOR AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - HOT WATER OFF FOR A WEEK FL. (Box Box 35)
  - VISITING WRITERS SERIES AT GMU PR/ C.I. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU OFFERS DAY - LONG LOGISTICS COURSES P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - PROMINENT ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING JOINS GMU FACULTY P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - TWO LOCAL BUSINESSMEN JOIN GMU BOARD OF VISITORS P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU ALUMNI ASSOCIATION INSTALLS NEW OFFICERS P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - YALE UNIVERSITY BIOLOGY PROFESSOR NAMED ROBINSON PROFESSOR AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - RETURNING NURSES CAN UPDATE SKILLS AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - METRO CAMPUS ASBESTOS TO BE REMOVED P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - POWER OUTAGE FL. (Box Box 35)
  - NEW STUDENT PICNIC AT GMU M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - AN EXHIBIT OF PERUVIAN ART AT GEORGE MASON METRO CAMPUS GALLERY C.I. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON'S HOMECOMING CELEBRATION WELCOMES HOME THE ALUMNI C.I. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON'S COMMUNITY COLLEGE EDUCATION PROGRAM RECEIVES FEDERAL MONEY P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - RADAR TO DETER CAMPUS SPEEDERS P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON CREATES NEW VICE PRESEDENT FOR COMMUNITY AND CORPORATE RELATIONS P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - FACULTY ART EXHIBIT GEORGE MASON'S FENWICK LIBRARY GALLERY P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - INTERNATIONALLY - KNOWN GEOPHYSICIST NAMED ROBINSON PROFESSOR AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - BOARD OF VISITORS RETREAT M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - CIT - FUNDED RESEARCH AT GMU TOTALS $ 3.3 MILLION. (Box Box 35)
  - CONSTRUCTION SITE DANGER FL. (Box Box 35)
  - BOARD OF VISITORS MEETING AT GMU M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON DISABILITY ACTIVITY TO BE HELD AT GMU. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU VICE PRESEDENT APPOINTED TO NATIONAL OFFICE. (Box Box 35)
  - VIRGINIA INITIATIVES MEETING M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON STUDENT GALLERY FEATURES LOCAL LANDSCAPE ARTIST P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON STUDENTS SPONSOR ALCOHOL AWARENESS WEEK P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - NEW RECTOR TO LEAD GMU GOVERNING BOARD P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON PRESENTS TOM PETERS IN AN INTERACTIVE TELECONFERENCE P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON HOLDS OPEN HOUSE FOR PROSPECTIVE STUDENTS P.R. / P.S.A. (Box Box 35)
  - COLLOQUIUM ON RACE AND ETHNIC RELATIONS AT GEORGE MASON P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - COLLEGE STUDENTS TO ATTEND BLACK LEADERSHIP CONFERENCE AT GEORGE MASON P.R. /P.S.A. (Box Box 35)
  - POWER OUTAGE FL. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU STUDENTS TO PROVIDE HALLOWEEN "WITCH WATCH" FOR NEIGHBORING COMMUNITY P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU HOSTS CONFERENCE ON QUANTUM THEORY AND CONCEPTIONS OF THE UNIVERSITY M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU NAMES GENERAL MANAGER FOR NEW ARTS CENTER ON CAMPUS P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - SOVIET DEBATE TEAM'S FIRST AMERICAN STOP IS GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GOV. ROBB'S U.S. SENATE CAMPAIGN COMES TO GEORGE MASON M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - FREE TICKETS TO THE MOSCOW CIRCUS FL P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU STUDENT RECEIVES FULBRIGHT FELLOWSHIP P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - MAURICE DAWKINS TO GIVE CAMPAIGN SPEECH AT GMU P.R. M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - TWO BANKERS HEAD GMU GALA COMMITTEE P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU ENROLLMENT UP 4.7 PERCENT P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU SPONSORS LOCAL GOVERNMENT FORM ON NORTHERN VIRGINIA P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - JUSTICE GOLDBERG WILL SPEAK AT GMU ON RELIGION AND THE FIRST AMENDMENT P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU ALUMNUS RETURNS AS ALUMNI ADMINISTRATOR P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - COLLAGES IN VARIOUS MEDIA ON EXHIBIT IN GEO. MASON FENWICK GALLERY P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GOSPEL FEST '88 PLANNED AS SCHOLARSHIP FUNDRAISER P.R. / P.S.A. (Box Box 35)
  - WATER OFF AT KING HALL FL. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEET M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - MITCH SNYDER, BENEFIT CONCERT AT GMU HIGHLIGHT CONCERN FOR HOMELESS C.I. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU ALUMNUS MAKES DONATION TO ESTABLISH SCHOLARSHIP FUND P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - BENNETT OF RUNAWAY FATHER SIGNS BOOKS AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - PARKING POLICY CHANGES N.R. (Box Box 35)
  - SHENANDOAH LANE CLOSES FROM DEC.12TH FL. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU SCHOOL OF NURSING HOLDS OPEN HOUSE P.R. / P.S.A. (Box Box 35)
  - COMM. RECOMMENDS MAJOR RECONSTRUCTION AND INCREASED PROGRAMS P.R. / M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - NAACP DIRECTOR BENJAMIN HOOKS TO SPEAK FOR GMU'S MARTIN LUTHER KING DAY OBSERVANCE P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON SCHOLAR PEGGY ALLEN OF BLACKSBURG GOES TO WASHINGTON P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - EIGHT GMU NURSING STUDENTS RECEIVE SCHOLARSHIPS FROM SIBLEY HOSPITAL P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - PHYSICAL PLANT OPENS WORK CONTROL CENTER FL. (Box Box 35)
  - BOARD OF VISITORS MEETING TUESDAY JAN. 17TH AT 4 P.M. M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU SCHOOL OF NURSING PINS 53 STUDENTS P.R. / M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU HOLDS STUDENT FINANCIAL AID WORKSHOP P.R. / P.S.A. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU STUDENTS NAMED TO DISTINGUISHED WHO'S WHO HONOR ROLL P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - LEADING SCHOLAR OF LATIN AMERICA NAMED ROBINSON PROFESSOR AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU APPOINTED DIRECTOR OF MEDIA RELATIONS P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - TRAFFORD RESIDENT NAMED TO DEAN'S LIST AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - ALCOHOL STUDY CONDUCTED BY GMU PROFESSOR P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - KOREAN UNIVERSITY PRESIDENT SIGNS AGREEMENT WITH GMU M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU PLANS MONTH LONG CELEBRATION OF BLACK HISTORY P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - VOLUNTEERS NEEDED TO HELP STAFF TEEN ALCOHOL / DRUG ABUSE PROGRAM P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - AT AGE 59, GMU NURSING PROFESSOR IS IN THE ARMY NOW P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - VISITING WRITERS SERIES CONTINUES AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GEORGE MASON'S DRINKING FOUNTAINS SAFE P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU PLANS "CAREERS UNLIMITED" SEMINARS AND JOBS FAIR P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU TO HOST CONFERENCE ON FRATERNITIES P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU ONCE AGAIN SPONSORS TRIP TO SOVIET UNION P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU HOSTS HIGH TECH JOB FAIR AT METRO CAMPUS P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - STEPHEN JAY GOULD, NOTED ANTHROPOLOGIST, TO SPEAK AT GMU. (Box Box 35)
  - NOBEL LAUREATE JAMES BUCHANAN TO SPEAK AT GMU'S ECONOMICS CLUB P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU ANNOUNCES DEAN'S LIST P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - CONFLICT RESOLUTION PROFESSORSHIP FUNDED AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - DON BEYER JR. BRINGS LT. GOV. CAMPAIGN TO GMU M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU HOSTS GOVERNMENT CONTRACTS SEMINAR P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - GMU CELEBRATES BICENTENNIAL OF FRENCH REVOLUTION P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - SHAULL BAKHASH, LEADING EXPERT ON IRAN, TO SPEAK AT GMU M.A. (Box Box 35)
  - SOVIET CONDUCTOR TO BE GMU VISITING PROFESSOR IN APRIL P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - 8TH GRADERS PLAN AHEAD FOR COLLEGE IN EARLY ID PROGRAM AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - HODDING CARTER TO SPEAK AT GMU'S INTERNATIONAL WEEK P.S.A. / P.R. (Box Box 35)
  - DEADLINE FOR FY88-89 PURCHASES FL. (Box Box 36)
  - 1988 ELECTION POST - MORTEM LECTURE SERIES AT GMU TO FEATURE PROMINENT JOURNALIST AND MEDIA CRITIC P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - CONGRESSWOMAN PAT SCHROEDER TO ADDRESS GMU'S " WOMEN IN LEADERSHIP " SEMINAR P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - MASON BASKETBALL MAKES TOURNAMENT FINALS FL. (Box Box 36)
  - CELEBRATE WITH THE CHAMPIONS FL. (Box Box 36)
  - PATRIOTS NCAA TOURNAMENT GAME ON CHANNEL 56 FL. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU ANNOUNCES COLLOQUIA OF GLOBAL ISSUES P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS TO MEET M.A. (Box Box 36)
  - NO. VA. WRITING PROJECT STUDENT SUMMER INSTITUTE OFFERED BY GMU P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU AND ARLINGTON COUNTY NAME NEW COMMITTEES P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU SPONSORS COLLEGE FAIR FOR HIGH SCHOOL JUNIORS P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU TO RAISE PARKING FINES P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - COVENANT HOUSE FOUNDER TO SPEAK AT GMU M.A. (Box Box 36)
  - NO AIR CONDITIONING UNTIL APRIL 7 FL. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU NOW ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS FOR "EXCEL" P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU NOW ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS FOR SUMMER SCHOOL P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - INSTITUTE FOR STRING TEACHING NOW ACCEPTING APPLICATIONS P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - ALUMNI EVENTS P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU FACULTY MEMBER NAMED TO ACE FELLOWSHIP POST P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - BIOINFORMATICS COMES TO GMU P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS APRIL 10 M.A. (Box Box 36)
  - CUTLINES - ADMISSIONS TOURS P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU RELEASES STUDY IN HIGHER EDUCATION IN VIRGINIA P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU RECEIVES GRANT TO RESEARCH TRAFFIC CONGESTION P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - TUITION AND FEES UP 12.35 % AT GMU FOR 1989 - 90 (Box Box 36)
  - GMU FRATERNITY SERVICE PROJECT BENEFITS NORTHERN VIRGINIA TRAINING CENTER P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - ELLIOT ABRAMS, FORMER ASSISTANT SECRETARY OF STATE, TO SPEAK AT GMU P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - LITERARY COMPETITION WINNERS ANNOUNCED BY MARY ROBERTS RINEHART FUND P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - PATRIOT CIRCLE CLOSED APRIL 30TH FL. (Box Box 36)
  - SPRAYING FOR GYPSY MOTHS FL. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU PROFESSOR WINS Guggenheim FELLOWSHIP P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU'S SCHOOL OF BUSINESS ADMIN RECEIVES ACCREDITATION P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU TO GRADUATE LARGEST CLASS P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU SPONSORS NUCLEAR WAR AND PEACE CONFERENCE P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU ANNOUNCES DEPARTURE OF CENTER FOR INTERACTIVE MANAGEMENT P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - VCCS CHANCELLOR HOCKADAY TO TEACH GMU SUMMER COURSE P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - LOCAL GRADUATE RECEIVES AWARD FROM GMU P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS MEETS MAY 16TH. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU TO HOST CONFERENCE ON EUROPEAN MARKET P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GOVERNOR'S ASIAN STUDIES / LANGUAGE ACADEMY INTRODUCES STUDENTS TO ORIENTAL CULTURES P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU SPONSORS FIFTH ANNUAL SENIOR WELLNESS WALK. (Box Box 36)
  - MASON SCHOLARS PROGRAM P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU PROFESSOR AWARDED FORD FOUNDATION FELLOWSHIP P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - HOT WATER OUTAGE P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU SPONSORS SUMMER PROGRAMS FOR STUDENTS WITH LEARNING DIFFICULTIES P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU OFFERS OPPORTUNITY FOR COMMUNITY TO LIST OFF - CAMPUS HOUSING VACANCIES P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU BOARD OF VISITORS SELECTS DOCTORAL CANDIDATE AS STUDENT REPRESENTATIVE P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - MOVE NEWS: MATERIAL MANAGEMENT MOVES TO 4087 UNIVERSITY DRIVE P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU LIBRARY ART GALLERY TO FEATURE WORKS OF IRISH POET, WILLIAM BUTLER YEATS. (Box Box 36)
  - GMU OFFERS "COMPUTER CAMP" CLASSES FOR LEARNING DISABLED ELEMENTARY STUDENT. (Box Box 36)
  - CAMP MASON '89 SET FOR JULY AND AUGUST P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - DEPOSITS TO CASHIER BY JUNE 30TH P.R. (Box Box 36)
  - STUDY BY GMU PROFESSOR SHOWS HIGH RADON LEVELS IN PRIVATE WELL WATER P.R. (Box Box 36)